The SCOAN Sunday Service
Somebody scream!
Hallelujah!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
There is something that makes me come into Your presence
My Helper
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Come on!
As we continue to relax
In Your precious arms
Holy Ghost
As we continue to relax
In Your precious arms
Holy Ghost
Come on! The best is yet to come.
The best is yet to come
Always
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you.
The atmosphere is charged now.
So before we begin to pray, if I may quickly remind you once again:
We believe 10 million people will have moved to the hospital, to the orphanage home,
all over the world to the less privileged, to the physically challenged.
Please move.
Bless people with your love.
Bless people with your care, your money, whatever God has given to you - move!
There are some troubled nations.
People that have access to go there, you need faith to bless people.
You can't just go on your own, "Hey, I have millions of dollars".
You need faith to bless people.
If that blessing is for God, you are blessing them - through them to God.
So you have to pay some price.
Apart from giving, you need grace to do it.
People are moving all over the world as I'm talking.
People are moving blessing people, giving a kiss to the old people.
Give them love and tell them, "Look, Jesus loves you".
Someone is waiting for you. Tell your neighbor to rescue them.
Someone is waiting for you, to pay their house rent.
Someone is waiting for you, for feeding.
Someone is waiting for you, for good health.
Someone is waiting for you, for freedom.
Someone is waiting for you, for blessing.
Someone is waiting for you, for reconciliation.
Not just because of my birthday.
My birthday just brought that awareness.
It is what you are supposed to be doing.
That is the life God designed for you because you are an angel -
angel of God to give love;
angel of God to give blessing;
angel to give more healing, deliverance.
You have not been doing this.
You have been looking at the face to do.
"This one hates me, I won´t give. This one loves me, let me give." No!
If you are an angel of God, you don't look at the face.
"This one loves me, this one is my family, I will give."
"This one hates me - no, no, no, I don't want to hear anything."
"This one is keeping malice. No."
No!
Love your neighbor as yourself.
Your neighbor could be your enemy,
your neighbor could be those who do not share the same faith with you.
Love them all.
Hallelujah!
Rise up for prayer.
Right now, open your lips.
Jesus loves you.
Open your lips.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Father, we ask for sanctification.
Sanctify us, in the name of Jesus.
Right now, be open. Come out.
God is not a man.
Be open.
He is not a man.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Be open.
God is not a man.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
How do you open?
To be open is to mean what you are saying.
Don't just begin to talk. You must mean what you are saying.
It is time to reconcile.
What you cannot tell man, tell God.
Here I am; use me.
Here I am; send me.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Yes, I give a warning.
This is warning, red card to the evil spirit right now.
Come out! I say out!
You evil spirit, leave my people!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Leave my people!
Today, satan is under your foot.
You know it; I know it.
The cause of sickness - under your foot!
The cause of disappointment - under your foot!
The cause of setback - under your foot!
The cause of disease - under your foot!
The cause of nightmare - under your foot!
March!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah!
Viewers all over the world, say, "I am a child of God!"
By the grace of God, I am a child of God!
By the righteousness of God, I am a child of God!
You demon, I command you, in the name of Jesus!
I command you right, left and back -
I command you to leave my life, business, career and family!
Prayer!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith And Receive
Right now say, "I am a child of God!"
You devil, in the name of Jesus, I command you out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Out!
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, where can you go from His presence?
Say after me:
You devil, I know you. You satan, I know you. I am a child of God!
I know you, you are a devil.
I know you, you are a killer.
I know you, you are a destroyer.
I know you, you are a thief.
I kick you out of my life!
Be kicked, in the name of Jesus!
I command you, in the name of Jesus, by the authority in the name Jesus, out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood & Poisonous Substances
I will not talk!
No affection in the marriage!
Who is the cause?
I´m the one. I've said I will not talk.
How did you enter her?
I entered her since childhood.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Open your lips and say to the devil: I know you; you are a killer!
I know you; you are a destroyer!
I know you; you are a thief!
I command you, in the name of Jesus!
Kick! Begin to kick the devil out!
I kick you! Come on! Leave my life!
Open your lips! Begin to kick the devil!
Come on! I kick you!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus!
Out!
Viewers, wherever you are right now, satan is under your foot.
You know it and I know it.
You know satan is a killer, thief, destroyer; he is under your foot.
March it right now, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to march it!
Viewers at home,
march the cause of sickness, disease, affliction, setback, disappointment and limitation.
I march you and I will continue to march you.
I march you and I will continue to walk on you.
Right now, you are under my foot; remain under my foot!
In the name of Jesus, you will remain under my foot.
In the name of Jesus, the cause of disappointment, remain under my foot!
In the name of Jesus, the cause of setback, remain under my foot!
In the name of Jesus, the cause of disease, sickness, affliction, remain under my foot!
The cause of nightmares, remain under my foot!
Right now in the name of Jesus! Hallelujah!
Viewers, wherever you are, whatever you are doing at this moment,
I don't know the period, the hour you are in.
Those of you under the influence of my voice right now, satan is under your foot!
I say you have silenced his voice;
his voice of sickness has been silenced;
his voice of disease has been silenced;
his voice of limitation has been silenced;
his voice of failure has been silenced;
In the name of Jesus!
I pray he remains under your foot, in Jesus' name
Thank You, Lord.
Right now, your country; the flag of your country. Remember your country.
God's intervention.
Whatever way satan is using to attack your nation
with corruption, misappropriation, idolatry, killing, stealing, destruction,
right now, in the name of Jesus, be seized!
Right now, begin to cover your nation with the Blood of Jesus.
Cover your nation with the Blood of Jesus!
Cover your country with the Blood of Jesus!
Thank You, Lord. Wave your hand.
Trouble spot nation.
There are some nations that have so much crisis right now; remember them in prayer.
Open your lips and remember them in prayer.
Prayer!
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Father, we thank You. Holy Spirit, we thank You.
Give thanks to Him for your deliverance, blessing, victory today. Jesus loves you.
TT Monica Asefa
RV: Mel Flowers 21/02/2019